<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<sst xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/spreadsheetml/2006/main" count="124" uniqueCount="100"><si><t>Description</t></si><si><t>PURCHASE ORDER</t></si><si><t>SREE HOLDINGS</t></si><si><t>NO 11, A WING,DIVYASREE CHAMBERS,</t></si><si><t>O SHAUGNESSY ROAD</t></si><si><t>BANGALORE - 560025</t></si><si><t>PROJECT:</t></si><si><t>BELLE VUE-PHASE 2</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">PO No:     </t></si><si><t>Date:</t></si><si><t>MIS No:</t></si><si><t>MIS Date:</t></si><si><t>To</t></si><si><t>DELIVERY ADDRESS</t></si><si><t>Sl No</t></si><si><t>UOM</t></si><si><t>Quantity</t></si><si><t>Rate</t></si><si><t>Amount</t></si><si><t>Req Date</t></si><si><t>Total</t></si><si><t>Narration:</t></si><si><t>Terms &amp; Conditions:</t></si><si><t>Authorised Signatory</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">All materials supplied will be subject to inspections &amp; test when received at our site. </t></si><si><t>Final Bill shall be cleared after Certification by the Concerned Engg &amp; on actual measurements taken at Site.</t></si><si><t>If any Goods damaged or rejected must be replaced inimediately at the suppliers own expenses.</t></si><si><t>Contact Person for Material Supply Mr. Sreedhar - 9972805 138</t></si><si><t>All Bills and DCs should contain the Reference of the Concerned PO .</t></si><si><t>SURVEY NO. 66P, BROADACRES STUDFARM</t></si><si><t>AVALAHALLI ESTATE,NEAR CRPF BUS STOP</t></si><si><t>YELAHANKA POST, BENGALURU - 560066.</t></si><si><t>TIN No: 29860610445</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">We hereby place an order on you for supply of the following materials subject to the terms &amp; conditions 
mentioned below. Deliveries should be as per delivery schedule. Deliveries must be accompanied by challan &amp; invoice in duplicate quoting this  order number, otherwise goods will not be accepted. Delivery challan and invoice should contain the delivery address.    </t></si><si><t>No</t></si><si><t>+14.5% VAT</t></si><si><t>UNNATHI ENTERPRISES</t></si><si><t>#5, 2nd B Cross Near Srinivasa Kalyanamantapa</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">mathikere, Extn, </t></si><si><t>Bangalore - 54</t></si><si><t>Ph: +91 080 23254731</t></si><si><t>Mob : 9986004163</t></si><si><t>TIN No: 29950884275</t></si><si><t>Transportation</t></si><si><t>Contact details of Supplier: Mr. Venkatesh : 9986004163</t></si><si><t>Prices are inclusive of Tax &amp; Transportation &amp; fixing.</t></si><si><t>Supply of Convex mirror.</t></si><si><t>Bill Requirement: Bill must carry details of Specific Purchase order number, site acceptance signature along with seal, buyer and supplier Tin number, Bill number, Cst Number, Transporter Chillan etc.(whichever is applicable)</t></si><si><t>PBVP20013</t></si><si><t>Mail Request</t></si><si><t>40" Polycarbonate Convex Mirror with fibre moulding, waterproof &amp; weather Proof.</t></si><si><t>Pole for above with primer and black enamel paint with fixing</t></si><si><t>Payment : Against supply.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">PO Req No: </t></si><si><t>Project:</t></si><si><t>Quantity Certification: Quantity mentioned in the Order may be approximate, actual &amp; mutually certified measurement will be accounted for the payment.</t></si><si><t>Bill Requirement: Bill must carry details of Specific Order number, site acceptance signature along with seal,buyer and supplier GST number,HSN Code, Bill number, LUT details, Transporter challan etc.</t></si><si><t>Price Escalation: Above mentioned in price is absolute frozen for this Order, in case of any price escalation " after" or "before/ in-between" will be considered breach of Contract terms &amp; will not be entertained.</t></si><si><t>Cancellation: Time is of the essence in this order. Buyer reserves the right to cancel this order, or any portion of this order, without liability, if; (1) delivery is not made when and as specified; (b) Seller fails to meet contract commitments as to exact time, price, quality or quantity</t></si><si><t>Any dispute or difference which may arise between the parties or their representatives shall be referred to two arbitrators to be nominated by each of the dissenting parties and the decision of the arbitrators shall be final and binding on the concerned parties and the proceedings shall be governed by the Arbitration and Conciliation Act 1996. All disputes shall be subject to jurisdiction of courts at Bangalore.</t></si><si><t>b. Contract Value Clause: - From the date of GST implementation during the tenure of contract, Basic Price mentioned in the contract to be taken before all the central and state levies which will be subsumed into GST.  All the intermediary credits that have been availed by the vendor, and all the non-creditable tax costs included in the basic price (including but not limited to excise duty, CVD, SAD, CST, Entry Tax, Octroi, etc. which will no longer be a cost under the GST regime) have to be passed on to us and the same will be adjusted to arrive at the Revised Basic Price for the purpose of computation of GST thereon at the applicable rates.  Necessary documentation and break-up of non-creditable tax costs included in the current Basic Price have to be provided to us for confirming to correctness of the Revised Basic Price</t></si><si><t>c. Penalty Clause: - In the penalty clause, it could be mentioned that GST as may be applicable on such penalty shall also be payable by the vendor.</t></si><si><t>GST TERMS:-</t></si><si><t>BCIM ENGINEERING PRIVATE LIMITED</t></si><si><t>d. TDS Clause: - TDS as may be applicable under the Income Tax Laws and the GST Laws shall be deducted by M/s. BCIM ENGINEERING PRIVATE LIMITED Sat the applicable rates. Also, TDS deducted under Income Tax and GST laws shall be mutually exclusive.</t></si><si><t>Grand Total</t></si><si><t>Sub Total</t></si><si><t>NOTE: 3 Copies of Tax invoice (original, duplicate &amp; triplicate) to be submitted along with each consignment supply</t></si><si><t>Order to be acknowledged and accepted or to be reverted if any changes within 4hours, If not it will be considered as accepted</t></si><si><t>Checked by</t></si><si><t>We hereby place an order on you for supply of the following materials with same terms and conditions as per original order.</t></si><si><t>We at BCIM are an environment friendly health and safety conscious organisation, therefore we expect you as our business associate to provide us with all the environment friendly materials &amp; services.</t></si><si><t>Also please ensure that your material during transit to us does not result in any environmental pollution and issues, Also ensure adequate package protection to prevent any damages to the material. As part of health and safety requirement please ensure that all chemicals consignment are accompanied by MSDS (Material safety data sheet) related to the chemicals.</t></si><si><t>Ensure compliances to all statutory and regulatory requirements of environment and health and safety including vehicle being certified for emission controls operated by licenced drivers and ensure covering the materials so that do not emit any fugitive dust / emissions to environment.</t></si><si><t>PO Req Date:</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Approval No: </t></si><si><t>Where the material generate dust, that could pollute atmosphere during the transit, supplier shall ensure to cover the truck transporting the material securely and safely to ensure there is no fugitive dust emission during the transit.</t></si><si><t>To,</t></si><si><t>Managing Director</t></si><si><t>"B" Wing, Divyasree Chambers.</t></si><si><t>No. 11, O'Shaugnessy Road, Bangalore - 560025</t></si><si><t>GSTIN : 29AAHCB6485A1ZL</t></si><si><t>DIVYASREE TQS</t></si><si><t>Project: TQS</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">YNT 63, Survey No. 5/3 &amp; 6/1, </t></si><si><t>Mandalakunte Village, Chikkabommasandra</t></si><si><t>Yelahanka Hobli, Near Mother Dairy</t></si><si><t>Contact Person: Mr. Ananthan 73036 75533</t></si><si><t>Bangalore 560065</t></si><si><t>DELIVERY ADDRESS:-</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">                          Director</t></si><si><t>Payment : 60Days from the date of supply</t></si><si><t>Lead Time : Within 2-3days from the date of order</t></si><si><t>Contact details of Supplier: Mr. Yusuf / Venkat (Mob: 95916 37906)</t></si><si><r><t xml:space="preserve">a. Payment Clause: - In an event of denial of credits to M/s. BCIM ENGINEERING PRIVATE LIMITED arising, on account of any non-payment of taxes or non-compliance with the GST Laws by the Vendor, BCIM ENGINEERING PRIVATE LIMITED shall withhold such amounts from the subsequent payments to the M/s. </t></r><r><rPr><b/><sz val="10"/><color theme="1"/><rFont val="Book Antiqua"/><family val="1"/></rPr><t>Power Tools &amp; Tackles</t></r><r><rPr><sz val="10"/><color theme="1"/><rFont val="Book Antiqua"/><family val="1"/></rPr><t>., till the input tax credit so denied is reinstated and reflected in the returns of BCIM ENGINEERING PRIVATE LIMITED In such cases BCIM ENGINEERING PRIVATE LIMITED shall be entitled to recover interest at the percent as specified in the Act and as amended time to time</t></r></si><si><t>HEADS</t></si><si><r><rPr><b/><u/><sz val="10"/><color indexed="8"/><rFont val="Book Antiqua"/><family val="1"/></rPr><t>Narration:</t></r><r><rPr><sz val="10"/><color indexed="8"/><rFont val="Book Antiqua"/><family val="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve"> Additional Safety &amp; Consumables for TQS</t></r></si><si><t>GST @ 5% on Item No. 6</t></si><si><t>GST @ 18% on item no.1-5, 7-27 items</t></si><si><t>Rupees:  One Lakh Sixty-Five Thousand Three Hundred &amp; Two Only.</t></si></sst>